ALIKSEI TKACHUK

Proactive, highly motivated and experienced Java Software Engeneer with 5 years of experience in Java. I am ambitious person, love to develop and increase my experience, skills and expertise, open-minded and always ready for the new challenges.



EXPERIENCE

Belarus (Misnk) January 2019 - Present

Java Software Engineer

Capsilon

Developed and enhanced Capsilon products for mortgage industry of United States of America. Was responsible for building and designing backend services for our applications, with good scalability and performance.

Technological stack: Java 11, Spring Webflux , GraphQI , Jenkins, Docker, Kubernetes , Maven

Belarus (Minsk)

January 2018 - January 2019

Software Automation Engineer

Capsilon

Was responsible for the automation process and approaches for company products. Designed from scratch many automation frameworks, core functionality united in strong tools for maintaining high quality of product. Worked as independent and also in team.

Technological stack : Selenide, Java 8, Spring Boot, Jenkins, Maven

Belarus (Minsk)

April 2017 - November 2017

Java Software Engineer

EPAM Systems

Worked on Epam project UPSA as Java software Engineer, wrote and developed internal company application for managing and stuffing employees, projects lifecycle and many other.

Technological stack: Java 8, MyBatis, JSP, MySql, Maven, Thymeleaf

Belarus (Minsk) April 2015 - March 2017

Sofware Autmotation Engineer

Epam Systems

Worked on two projects (MTVI and UPSA). Was responsible for writing and designing automation scripts and frameworks, run and analyzing them, creating reports and inhancing the quality of the product.

Technological stack : Java 8, Selenuim Webdriver, Hibernate, SQL, Maven, Test NG

EDUCATION

Belarus (Minsk) 2016

Bachelor of Mechanics and MAthematics

Belausian State University

CONTACT INFORMATION

Email

alikseitkachuk@gmail.com

Address

Belarus - Minsk

Phone

+375(29)606-10-59

SKILLS

RESTful WebServices

Java 11

Sping WebFlux

Spring Data

Spring Security

Spring Boot

Hibernate

PostgresQI

Sql

Jenkins

Thymeleaf & JSP

Git

Docker

ReactJS (without production experience)

GraphQI

LANGUAGES

English

Intermediate

Russian

Native